MARIAM REVAZISHVILI

DEVELOPER WEB



1 +995 591 05 97 40



revazishvili.mariam26@gmail.com

SKILLS

- HTML and CSS
- JavaScript
- ReactJS
- SQL
- mySQL
- popSQL
- Front End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- Strong Communication

EDUCATION

UDEMY CERTIFICATE:

React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux) -Maximilian Schwarzmuller October 2022 -present

UDEMY CERTIFICATE:

The Complete JavaScript Course 2022 - Jonas Schmedtmann June-July 2022

IT ACADEMY STEP:

Front-End development (Beginner Course) (HTML, CSS, JavaScript Fundamentals)

July 2021 - December 2021

TBILISI STATE UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of International Law 2015-2019

PROFILE

As a fast learning, team playing, high energy individual, I posses all the qualities and eagerness to succeed in a web development role. My experience aligns with the requirements for the role and I look forward to the opportunity to use my skills to develop your company and progress my skills in line with the company's objectives.

EXPERIENCE

LLC PUBLIC AUDIT INSTITUTE

legal assistant 2016 - 2017

STATE AUDIT OFFICE OF GEORGIA

legal assistant 2017-2018

SNAP FITNESS GEORGIA

Administrative Manager 2019-2021

LANGUAGES

GEORGIAN - NATIVE ENGLISH - FLUENT RUSSIAN - PROFICIENT GREEK - PROFICIENT GERMAN-BASIC



METLIFY